<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>FlowSynx Blog</title>
        <link>https://flowsynx.io/blog</link>
        <description>FlowSynx Blog</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[FlowSynx v1.1.2 is now available]]></title>
            <link>https://flowsynx.io/blog/flowsynx-v1.1.2-is-now-available</link>
            <guid>https://flowsynx.io/blog/flowsynx-v1.1.2-is-now-available</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[FlowSynx v1.1.2 is officially released!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FlowSynx v1.1.2 is officially released!</p>
<p>We're excited to roll out version 1.1.2 of FlowSynx — our lightweight, secure, and plugin-driven workflow engine. This release focuses on performance improvements, stability enhancements, and continued support for scalable, no-code automation.</p>
<p>Thank you to the community and contributors helping shape FlowSynx into a powerful platform for orchestrating workflows across cloud and on-prem environments.</p>
<p>📦 Available now via <a href="https://github.com/flowsynx/flowsynx/releases" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">GitHub</a>, and <a href="https://hub.docker.com/r/flowsynx/flowsynx" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Docker</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>FlowSynx</category>
            <category>Release</category>
            <category>WorkflowAutomation</category>
            <category>NoCode</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Introducing the FlowSynx blog]]></title>
            <link>https://flowsynx.io/blog/introducing-the-flowsynx-blog</link>
            <guid>https://flowsynx.io/blog/introducing-the-flowsynx-blog</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Welcome to the FlowSynx blog!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Welcome to the FlowSynx blog!</strong></p>
<p>We’ve created this space to share FlowSynx news and a variety of content from and for the FlowSynx community. This content may include deep dives into specific technical topics, examples of how FlowSynx can be used in various scenarios, and other interesting contributions from the community.</p>
<p>Whether you're an experienced developer, a solution architect, or just getting started with FlowSynx, this blog is designed to offer insights, tips, and inspiration to help you get the most out of our platform. Expect regular updates covering topics such as:</p>
<ul>
<li>Behind-the-scenes updates on new features, roadmap items, and architectural decisions.</li>
<li>Step-by-step guides and tutorials to help you build and deploy your own custom workflows and plugins.</li>
<li>Use case spotlights showing how FlowSynx is being applied across different industries and real-world scenarios.</li>
<li>Community contributions including guest posts, extensions, integration ideas, and tips from users like you.</li>
<li>Best practices and design patterns to help ensure your solutions are robust, secure, and scalable.</li>
</ul>
<p>We believe in building together, and your feedback, questions, and ideas are not only welcome—they’re essential. We hope this blog becomes a valuable resource for learning, sharing, and connecting with others in the FlowSynx ecosystem.</p>
<p>Stay tuned, and thanks for being a part of the FlowSynx journey!</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>Introduction</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>